Guide to the Sue M. Durrant Papers 1956-2006
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Sue M. Durrant Papers
1956-2006
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
Cage 711
Durrant, Sue Marilynn, 1937-
12.5 Linear Feet of Shelf Space 24 boxes
Sue Durrant joined the faculty at Washington State University in 1962. She served as the head coach for women's volleyball from 1962 to 1975, as the instructor for the Fish Fans synchronized swim group from 1962 to 1968, and as head coach for women's basketball from 1971 to 1982. The collection includes materials related to Durrant's career and activities at WSU, including the Department of Physical Education for Women, the Physical Education Sports and Leisure Studies (PESLS) Department, women's basketball, volleyball, and the Fish Fans synchronized swim group
Sue Durrant was born in Salt Lake City, UT in 1937. She earned a bachelor's degree from the University of Utah (1959), a master's degree from Washington State University (1962) and a Ph.D. from The Ohio State University (1976).
Durrant joined the faculty at Washington State University in 1962. She served as the head coach for women's volleyball from 1962 to 1975, as the instructor for the Fish Fans synchronized swim group from 1962 to 1968, and as head coach for women's basketball from 1971 to 1982. In addition to her coaching and teaching duties, Durrant was instrumental in implementing the provisions of Title IX at Washington State University, serving on numerous committees. She helped establish the Northwest College Women's Sports Association (NCWSA) and was its president in 1970-71. This organization became Region IX of the Association for Intercollegiate Athletics for Women (AIAW). Title IX, passed in 1972, guaranteed women equal access to athletic opportunities. In 1978 Durrant became one of the lead plaintiffs in the case Blair v. WSU, in which student athletes and faculty members sued the university for equal opportunities for women. The case was tried in 1982. The initial decision, though in favor of the plaintiffs, exempted football from the calculations. This decision was appealed to the WA state Supreme Court. The Supreme Court ruled in 1987 that football must be included.
In 1983 Durrant became the first delegate from Washington State University to the Bryn Mawr Institute for Women in Higher Education Administration. From 1986 to 1989 she served as faculty representative to the state legislature in Olympia, and in 1986-1987 she was president of the Association for Faculty Women (AFW) at WSU. From 1990 to 1992 she served as chair of the Washington Council of Faculty Representatives. In 2001 she became the first recipient of the Samuel H. Smith Leadership Award, given by the AFW in recognition of her many years of dedication to the advocacy of equal status for women in the university.
The collection includes materials related to Durrant's career and activities at WSU, including the Department of Physical Education for Women, the Physical Education Sports and Leisure Studies (PESLS) Department, women's basketball, volleyball, and the Fish Fans synchronized swim group; advisory committees and faculty/staff meetings; the merger of the Departments of Physical Education for Men and Women; the Sport Management program; Legislative Affairs; the meetings of the Council of Faculty Representatives; and the Task Force on the Climate for Women at WSU. The collection includes correspondence, audiocassette tapes, photographs, newspaper articles, and memorabilia.
The collection is arranged in two series. Series 1 contains the majority of the materials and is arranged in a single sequence representing Durrant's original filing order. Series 2 includes audiocassettes and memorabilia.
This collection is open and available for research use.
Sue M. Durrant donated her papers to the WSU Libraries in 2006 (MS 2006-15).
Northwest College Women's Sports Association Records, 1940-2013 (Cage 795)
Washington State University Gender Equity Lawsuit Papers, 1969-2007 (Cage 954)
Preliminary Guide to the Joanne Washburn Papers, 1921-2001 (MS 2005.06)
Centennial Oral History Project Oral Histories, 1982-1988 (Archives 202)
Washington State University History 398 (History of Women in the American West) Student Projects, 1996-2005 (Archives 262)
Washington State University Womens Physical Education Department Records, 1973-1981 (Archives 300)
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Durrant, Sue Marilynn, 1937- --Archives
Washington State University. Department of Physical Education for Women.; Washington State University. Department of Physical Education and Athletics.; United States. -- Education Amendments of 1972. -- Title IX.
Women coaches (Athletics); Physical education for women.; Sex discrimination in sports -- Washington (State); Women athletes -- Washington (State); College athletes -- Washington (State); College sports -- Washington (State) -- Management.; Basketball for women.; Volleyball for women.; Synchronized swimming -- Washington (State) -- Pullman.
Sports and Recreation; Colleges and Universities; Women; Washington (State)
- Series 1: Office files, 1956-2006
  - Retirements, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Physical Education, College of Education; 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Coordinator Meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Professional Areas Committee (minutes), 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Physical Education Sports and Leisure Studies (PESLS), 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Professional Areas Committee (minutes), 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - PESLS, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Studies Committee (minutes), 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Studies Committee and Review, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
  - Graduate Studies Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - PESLS Strategic Planning, College of Education, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
  - PESLS Strategic Planning Report, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - PESLS Strategic Planning Committee Meetings, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
  - PESLS Strategic Planning Committee, 1984
    - Notes, SPC Meetings (Box 2, Folder 18-21)
    - RLS (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Teacher Preparation (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Sport Management (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Activity Course Program (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Graduate Program (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Others (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Athletic Training and Sport Medicine (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - SPC First Set (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - SPC Second Set (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - SPC Third Set (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Documents (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Graduate Studies Committee minutes and notes, 1983-1988 (Box 2, Folder 33-35)
  - Graduate Studies Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - PESLS awards and honors for students; 1987, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Faculty files
    - Faculty meetings and memos, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 38-40)
    - Ad hoc committee, Department Climate, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Miscellaneous Documents, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - PESLS tenure policies, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Faculty meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Advisory Committee, College of Education, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Faculty meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 46-47)
    - Practicum Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Strategic Planning Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Women's Physical Education (WPE) tenure committee, 1981-1987 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Forum: religion and other non-course related issues, 1984 January 24 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Sexual harassment information: articles, policies, legal background; 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - WSU Physical Education newsletters, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Physical Education, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Women's Physical Education staff meetings, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Physical Education meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Women's Physical Education, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Women's Physical Education, enrollment (major), 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - National Association for Girls and Women in Sports (NAGWS) Basketball Guidelines; 1981-1982, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Gender equity news articles, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Game schedules and memorabilia, photographs, etc.; 1982-1983, 1986, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Women's Athletics recruiting pamphlets, 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 62-64)
  - Article about Durrant, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence (general), 1972-1979 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Women's Athletics policies and procedures, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Hospitality Program (Women's basketball), 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Recruiting (samples), 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Player information, 1977-1981 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Basketball manager application forms (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Basketball philosophy articles and handouts (copies), circa 1970s (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Women's basketball organization, undated (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Program ideas, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Women's Athletics scholarship procedures, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - WSU Athletics articles, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - WSU Sports Information, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Fundraising, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Radio, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Women's Athletics awards events, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - The Challenge (WSU Women's Athletics newsletter), 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Basketball introductory meeting, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Managers: Game statistics workshop, undated (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Recruiting, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Basketball auditions, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Campus visitations, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Basketball home game information, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Scorer and Timer information (home games), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Worksheets and guidelines for doing statistics, undated (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Basketball Master Schedule, 1977-1981 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Basketball clinic information and miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Basketball scheduling; 1976-1977, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Volleyball and basketball scheduling; 1974-1975, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Volleyball, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Basketball, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 96-98)
  - Basketball, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Overlays (overhead transparencies), 1978 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Women's basketball
    - 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Play book, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Offense, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Defense, undated (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Out of bounds, undated (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - Drills, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Summer conditioning, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Women's Intercollegiate Forms 1970 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 109-111)
    - Expense reports, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - Opponent information, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - Individual player reports and line-up, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Giusti Tournament of Champions Program, 1979 December (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - Junior Varsity practices and game statistics, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - Junior Varsity, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Junior Varsity, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - Junior Varsity, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - "Fastbreak" (Seattle University), 1979 January (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - Yakima, 1979 August (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Basketball clinic, Kent, WA, 1977 October (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - Basketball coaching clinic, Montana State University, 1975 June (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - WIAA-NAHPER workshop, Kennewick, WA, 1975 March (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - Dorothea Coleman basketball clinic, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Dorothea Coleman basketball clinics-workshops; 1967, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - WSU v. New South Wales All Stars photographs, Jeanne Eggert, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Photographs, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - Photographs, WSU at Northwest Women's Basketball Tournament, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - Article about Gymnastics cut from the Evergreen, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Giusti Tournament, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 131-133)
    - NCAA official scorebook, varsity, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - NCAA official scorebook, varsity, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - NCAA official scorebook, junior varsity; 1979-1980, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - Volleyball invitational tournament, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - Volleyball summer conditioning, undated (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - High school volleyball tournament, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Workshop, Intermediate School District 167, 1974 September (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Volleyball clinics, 1969-1973 (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Volleyball clinic, Idaho Association of Health, Physical Education and Recreation, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - State volleyball workshops, Fall 1967 (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Women's Athletics, miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - National Sports Festival, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - National Sports Festival, Basketball West team, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 146-147)
  - Volleyball workshops, Fall 1967 (Box 8, Folder 148-149)
  - Fourth National Institute on Girls' Sports (basketball and volleyball), 1966 (Box 8, Folder 150-151)
  - Sport Management Program
    - Graduate program development, 2000-2003 (Box 8, Folder 152)
    - Graduate program development, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 153)
    - Internship manuals, 2000-2003 (Box 8, Folder 154)
    - Director information, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 155)
    - Advising lists and Sport Management majors, 1989-2004 (Box 8, Folder 156-157)
    - Interns, 2003-2005 (Box 8, Folder 158)
    - Graduation photographs, 2001-2005 (Box 8, Folder 159)
    - Alumni information, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 160)
    - Program brochure (Bill London), Fall 2001 (Box 8, Folder 161)
    - Newsletter; 1985, 2000-2002, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 162)
    - Sport Management Certification criteria; 1989, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 163)
    - Program review (BA in Sport Management), undated (Box 8, Folder 164)
    - Program review, 2002-2004 (Box 9, Folder 165-166)
    - Strategic Planning, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 167-168)
    - Merlin Computer Advising Program, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 169)
    - Marketing program, 1998 October (Box 9, Folder 170)
    - Senior Awards, Spring 2003 (Box 9, Folder 171)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 172)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 173-174)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 175)
    - Curriculum meetings, miscellaneous, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 176)
    - Summer 2001 (Box 9, Folder 177)
    - Meetings, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 178)
    - Standards and Review Protocol; Sport Management Program Review Council (SMPRC), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 179)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 180-181)
    - Historical background, accreditation information, 1984-1998 (Box 9, Folder 182-183)
    - Proposal, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 185-186)
    - Meetings, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 187)
    - Information Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 188)
    - Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 189)
    - Curriculum, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 190)
    - Leadership in College Athletics Programs; 1995-1996, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 191-192)
    - Educational Administration Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 193)
    - Technology, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 194)
    - Master's Degree, coaching, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 195-197)
    - Carol Gordon, WSU Athletic Hall of Fame, undated (Box 10, Folder 198)
  - Gordon-Enberg Professional Series
    - 1990 (Box 10, Folder 199)
    - "Fitness Is Your Business," 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 200)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 201)
    - "Women and the Olympics," 1984 (Box 10, Folder 203-204)
    - Budget, contributions; 1984 (Box 11, Folder 205-206)
    - Plans, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 207)
    - Contributions, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 208-209)
  - Placement Survey, 1979-1983 (Box 11, Folder 210)
  - Women's Physical Education
    - Staff meetings, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 211)
    - Staff meetings and miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 212)
    - Staff meetings and office information, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 213-214)
    - Minutes, committees, miscellaneous; 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 215-216)
    - Faculty meetings, committee assignments; 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 217)
    - Staff meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 218)
    - Women's Physical Education and Men's Physical Education, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 219)
  - Minors and Options Committee, 1972-1977 (Box 11, Folder 220)
  - Ethics Panel, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 221)
  - Professional Preparation Conference, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 222-223)
  - Sports Clinic, 1968 May (Box 12, Folder 224)
  - Women's Physical Education meetings
    - 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 225)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 226)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 227)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 228)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 229)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 230)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 231)
  - Joint Department staff meetings
    - 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 232)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 233)
    - 1964 (Box 12, Folder 234)
  - Men's Physical Education staff meeting, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 235)
  - College of Education staff meetings, 1962-1967 (Box 12, Folder 236)
  - Women's Physical Education
    - Majors handbook; 1972, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 237)
    - Newsletters, 1962-1968 (Box 12, Folder 238-239)
    - Philosophy of Physical Education, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 240)
    - Theses: WSU Departments of Physical Education for Men and Physical Education for Women, 1930-1964 (Box 12, Folder 241)
    - 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 242)
    - 1974-1979 (Box 13, Folder 243-244)
    - 1970-1974 (Box 13, Folder 245-247)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 248)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 249)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 250-252)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 253)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 254)
    - 1963-1954 (Box 13, Folder 255)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 256)
  - Inland Empire Board of Officials; basketball, volleyball; 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 257)
  - Officiating Clinic and Columbia Basin College, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 258)
  - Division for Girls and Women's Sports Volleyball Committee: the Principles and Techniques of Officiating; 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 259)
  - Volleyball Opinionnaires, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 260-261)
  - Fish Fans 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 262-263)
  - Fish Fans programs and photographs, 1962-1979 (Box 14, Folder 264)
  - Rhythm and Aquatics panel presentation, Northwest District, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 265)
  - Group Aqua Choreography, Oregon State University workshop, 1965 April (Note: see related audio recording in folder 429) (Box 14, Folder 266)
  - Synchronized swimming clinic, 1965 June (Box 14, Folder 267)
  - Task Force, Climate for Women, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 268-269)
  - Council of Faculty Representatives, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 270)
  - Council of Faculty Representatives, 1987 January (Box 14, Folder 271)
  - ICAO Meetings (notes), 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 272)
  - Commission on the Status of Women, 1971-1993 (Box 14, Folder 273)
  - Council of Faculty Representatives
    - 1988 (Box 15, Folder 274-277)
    - Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 278-279)
    - Letterhead (Box 15, Folder 280)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 281)
    - Legislative sessions, faculty salary issues; 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 282)
    - Legislative affairs, 1987-1992 (Box 15, Folder 283)
    - WSU, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 284)
    - Legislative information, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 285)
    - Bills, House of Representatives, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 286)
    - 1989-1992 (Box 15, Folder 287)
  - Gender Equality Education, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 288)
  - Student Athlete Handbook, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 289)
  - Intercollegiate Athletic Department Handbook (WSU basketball camp), 1983. (Box 16, Folder 290)
  - Athletics merger, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 291)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics administrative staff meetings, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 292)
  - Touchdown Illustrated magazine (WSU vs. OSU), 1982 October 9 (Box 16, Folder 293)
  - Women's basketball head coach search, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 294)
  - Women's basketball, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 295)
  - Women's intercollegiate athletics host family letters, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 296)
  - Hall of Fame, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 297)
  - Awards functions, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 298)
  - Miscellaneous articles (George Raveling), 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 299)
  - NOR-PAC, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 300-302)
  - NOR-PAC, PAC Athletic Conference handbook, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 303)
  - PAC-10 Conference Handbooks; 1982-1983, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 304)
  - NCAA Tournament, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 305)
  - NCAA Far West Regional Tournament photographs (WSU-University of Idaho hosts), undated (Box 17, Folder 306)
  - Joann Washam-Nancy Lopez Golf Clinic, Spokane, 1982 September (Box 17, Folder 307)
  - Touchdown Illustrated (WSU vs. NV-LV) 1983 September 24 (Box 17, Folder 307)
  - Golf World Weekly 1977 January 7 (Box 17, Folder 307)
  - Volleyball International Exhibition, undated (Box 17, Folder 308)
  - Basketball, Dial Classic, 1983 December 2-3 (Box 17, Folder 309)
  - Republic of China vs. WSU Women's Basketball and USSR vs. WSU Men's Basketball, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 310-318)
  - Recruiting Guide, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 319)
  - Financial Assistance statements (women), 1983 (Box 17, Folder 320)
  - Financial Assistance statements (men), 1983 (Box 17, Folder 321)
  - Ready Reference Chart for NCAA recruiting rules, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 322)
  - Meetings with coaching staff, recruiting; 1981-1984 (Box 17, Folder 323)
  - Athletic scholarships, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 324)
  - Meetings, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 325)
  - Athletic Department Monday Scoop Sheet, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 326)
  - Athletic Council, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 327)
  - Jesse Welch Seminar, 1983 (Note: please see related audiocassettes, folders 430-435) (Box 18, Folder 328)
  - Recruiting seminars, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 329)
  - "Effective Recruiting: The Competitive Edge in Women's" Athletics seminar, 1982 (Note: please see related audiocassette, folder 436) (Box 18, Folder 330)
  - Recruiting mini sessions, 1983 (Note: please see related audiocassettes, folders 437-440) (Box 18, Folder 331)
  - George Selleck Sports recruiting workshop, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 332-333)
  - Volleyball team manager reports, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 334)
  - Volleyball camp planning, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 335)
  - Prospective players letter (Box 18, Folder 336)
  - Australian Touring Team, New South Wales (Basketball), 1977 (Box 18, Folder 337)
  - GIUSTI Tournament, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 338)
  - Women's professional basketball, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 339)
  - Season evaluation forms, undated (Box 18, Folder 340)
  - Cage Camp brochures, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 341)
  - Correspondence, high school coaches, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 342)
  - Half-Time, 1977 November 5 (Box 18, Folder 343)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 344)
  - WSU Women's Basketball, 1975-1981
    - Team goals and season evaluation, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 345)
    - Basketball evaluation forms I, undated (Box 19, Folder 346)
    - Basketball evaluation forms II, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 347)
    - Player conference rosters; 1979-1980, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 348)
    - Interviews and evaluations, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 349)
    - Player information, 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 350)
    - Jeanne Eggert, Walla Walla High School, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 351)
    - Jeanne Eggert, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 352)